

Joaquín Urtasun

Mail: joakiurtasun@gmail.com

(54) 9 280 419 5492 Phone:

Address: Tehuelches 217, Puerto Madryn Chubut

Argentina (9120)

Proactivity

Skills

- Adaptability
- Good problem solving skills
- Kindness and good interpersonal relations

• Advanced English level

- Continuous learning and motivation to constantly improve
- Leadership skills
- · Team player
- · Ability to listen and learn from others
- Critical thinking

Professional Profile

Hello! My name is Joaquín, I'm a 21-year-old web developer with a degree in Computer Technology, and I also graduated from Henry Academy along with other web development courses I've taken. I have over 3 years of experience in software development and more than 2 years in the front-end sector, working with technologies such as React, CSS, HTML, JavaScript, TypeScript, Redux, WordPress, among others. I am also a Full-stack developer, so I can perform without any issues in the back-end sector.

Work experience

Full-Stack developer

FEPA | Octubre 2021- Marzo 2023

Marcos A. Zar 413, U9120 Puerto Madryn, Chubut / Contacto: +54 9 280 456 2082

Tasks performed: Review of applications to ensure stability and optimal performance; development of ideas for project creation; general assistance in the execution of these projects; overall support to the department.

Habilidades: Efficiency - Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) - HTML - Communication - Teamwork -Leadership.

Front-End developer (

Lilab | Junio 2023 - Agosto 2024

Contact: https://www.linkedin.com/company/limainnovationlab/mycompany/

Tasks performed: Worked with my team on the development of an application, handling the front-end. Skills: Teamwork - CSS - TypeScript - React - Problem-solving - Organization.

Education

Secondary education, School N728 Alfonsín Storni 2015 - 2021 Computer Technology, School N728 Alfonsín Storni 2019 - 2021 Conceptual and practical Web development course, FEPA 2021 Full-Time Intensive Full-Stack Web Development Course, Soy Henry 2023

What am I looking for as an employee?

I am looking for a dynamic and challenging environment where I can grow both personally and professionally, contributing as an active member of the team. I am passionate about my work, always seeking to improve and expand my knowledge. I consistently explore new technologies and trends to enhance my skills, ensuring that I stay up to date and can implement innovative solutions.

Idiomas

Spanish: Native **English:** Advanced Portuguese: Beginner

Corean: Started